Rebekah Querry Global Events and Product Development Manager

beckyquerry@gmail.com - 417.689.2529

Travel designer with over two decades of experience in the leisure vacation sector and entertainment. Increased customer base by 25 percent for the last two years through excellent vendor relations and personal design ideas. Have traveled to popular destinations to be able to speak first-hand about the laws, customs, and travel advisories. Among a staff of 15 Product Development Managers for over 650,000 members globally, with the department average of customized luxury trips of over 300 per month.

Areas of expertise include luxury travel, sales and event planning, organizing and managing events, managing logistics; shipping, hotels and room blocks, food and beverage and contract negotiations. Experienced in all aspects of event management and sales, traveling domestically and internationally as needed. Proven interpersonal skills: highly detailed minded with strong time-management and organizational skill set and ability to multi-task under pressure.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Product Development Manager

WorldVentures - Plano, TX - May 2015 to Present

- Led curating and procurement of the travel services and components of DreamTrips worldwide destinations from ideation to book ability
- Conducted research to identify new opportunities for bringing about innovation in events and designed unique luxury experiences for members
- Negotiate and contract luxury hotels, VIP events and excursions, event space and service providers for DreamTrips branded and organized events while successfully staying within budget
- Coordinated and managed event logistics, services and meeting requirements including: space allocation, transportation, room block, food and beverage and audio visual
- Successfully collaborated on RFPs and contracts for hotel, travel vendors, DMCs
- Procured \$450k in new accounts within 10 months and achieved 132% of a 4.6 million goal.
- Negotiated average savings of 40% in hotel and travel vendor contracts

Worldwide Events Manager

Enactus, Non-Profit Organization - Springfield, MO - May 2014 to May 2015

- Plan and execute the annual Enactus World Cup Event with over 5,000 attendees Held in Beijing, China 2014 and Johannesburg, South Africa, 2015. This premiere 3 day event brings top students, from all over the world, together to present their entrepreneurial social projects and to compete in front of a panel of global executives.
- Research, negotiate and manage all aspects of contract review and event space and service providers for Enactus including hotel contracts through partnership with Helms Briscoe, organized events domestically and internationally.
- Coordinate and manage event logistics, services and meeting requirements including: space allocation, 1,500+ room block, all international and domestic outbound and inbound shipping of event materials, food and beverage, audio visual and branding.
- Manage and maintain process of communicating accurate, complete and timely event information on the Events Website including timing of events, logistics information, hotel, dates, transportation and

Rebekah Querry Global Events and Product Development Manager

beckyquerry@gmail.com - 417.689.2529

location information.

- Manage all event related relationships with vendors, event sponsors and act as the onsite VIP handler for speakers and panelists.
- Create, implement and evaluate event processes in collaboration with function teams, production crew and teams to ensure sound structure, communication and operation of programs.

Vacations Specialist

Branson Tourism Center - Branson, MO - June 2012 to May 2014

- Sold specific travel packages, highlighted by BTC Travel, to promote business initiatives. Awarded consistent bonuses for exceeding sales goals for inbound calls and walk-in customers.
- Successfully developed and maintained an understanding of the client's and or company's business activities and the client's specific job function in order to build and maintain effective relationships.
- Effectively offered clients advice and or recommendations on ways to achieve improved travel plans at a more effective cost.
- Contacted the client on return to determine the success of the transaction and the client's feedback about product quality and ensure any required follow up steps were completed and outcomes reported.
- Thoroughly insured highest standard of presentation in all documentation for clients as well as a speedy and accurate response to any communications.

Event Manager and Entertainment Director

PCR Productions - Branson, MO - November 1989 to June 2009

- Directed over 300 performances/productions as Performance Director for a touring production company.
- Conducted research to identify new opportunities for bringing about innovation in events. Initiated contact with potential clients through outbound calls and direct mail.
- Managed and developed a strategic plan of action to ensure that the cost of the event remains under the pre-determined budget.
- Searched and negotiated suitable venues or locations as per the requirement and budgetary constraints of organization and/or client.
- Facilitated communication with professionals, including venue management, stand designers, caterers, contractors and equipment rentals to ensure efficient running of an event.
- Coordinated all aspects of fairs, festivals, trade shows and event-related logistics including; preplanning, booking talent, press releases, show services, marketing materials, contract negotiations with hotels and venues, budget management and post-show recaps.

EDUCATION

Business, Marketing/Management

Everest University at Tampa - Tampa, FL 2009 to 2011

Rebekah Querry Global Events and Product Development Manager

beckyquerry@gmail.com - 417.689.2529

SKILLS

Customer Service, Sales, Telecommunications, Event Management, Logistics, Sales Management, Training.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SKILLS: Advanced in Outlook, Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access, Sabre and SalesForce